[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
Okay, so far we've assumed that the only feature relevant to the value of my house,
حسنًا، حتى الآن فقد افترضنا أن الخاصية الوحيدة المتعلقة بقيمة منزلي،
is the square feet of the house.
هي مساحة المنزل بالقدم المربع.
But I dig into the data set a little bit more, and
ولكني تعمقت في مجموعة البيانات أكثر،
I look at a house that's supposed to be very similar to mine.
وفحصت منزلًا يفترض أنه يشبه منزلي جداً.
It's a house that has very similar square footage.
إنه منزل له مساحة مربعة مقاربة جدًا.
And so, this house is definitely making an influence on what the predictions are for
وبالتالي، فإن هذا المنزل له بالتأكيد تأثير على التوقعات الخاصة
my house.
بمنزلي.
But I look at it and I say, and I look at the specific listing, and
ولكني أنظر إليه وأقول وأنظر إلى القائمة المفصلة،
it shows that that house only had one bathroom.
وأجد أنها توضح أن هذا المنزل به حمامًا واحدًا
It's actually quite a big house, only one bathroom.
هو في الحقيقة منزل كبير، ولكنه يحتوي على حمام واحد.
And I say that's really, really not comparable to my house,
وأقول إن هذا المنزل فعلاً لا يمكن مقارنته بمنزلي،
which has three bathrooms.
الذي يحتوي على ثلاث حمامات.
So that the value of that house, that house sales price
ولذلك فإن قيمة هذا المنزل، سعر هذا المنزل
really shouldn't be indicative of what my house sales price should be.
لن يكون مؤشرًا مناسبًا لسعر البيع الخاص بمنزلي.
So instead what we can think about doing is adding more features.
ولذلك فيمكننا أن نفكر في إضافة خصائص أكثر.
So instead of just looking at the relationship between square feet and
فبدلًا من مجرد النظر إلى العلاقة بين مساحة المنزل بالقدم المربع و
price, we can add number of bathrooms.
السعر، يمكننا إضافة عدد الحمامات.
And now for
والآن بالنسبة إلى
each one of the listings that I looked at before, I'm gonna have to go through and
كل قائمة من التي فحصتها من قبل فإنه يتوجب علي أن أعيد فحصها
record how many square feet that house had, and the number of bathrooms.
وأسجل المساحة بالقدم المربع وعدد الحمامات.
And I'm gonna plot each of these points in the 3D space.
وأقوم بتوقيع كل واحدة من هذه النقاط على الفراغ ثلاثي الأبعاد.
Okay? So it's this hyper cube of square
حسنًا؟ ومن ثم نحصل على مكعب الفراغ هذا
feet versus bathrooms versus price.
المساحة بالقدم المربع ضد عدد الحمامات ضد السعر
And now instead of fitting a line to the data, if I'm thinking about just a very
والآن بدلًا من توصيل خط مناسب بين البيانات، فلو أنا فكرت في
simple model, I can think about fitting a hyper plane.
نموذج بسيط جدًا، فإني سوف أفكر في اختيار مستوى فائق.
Okay, so it's just a slice through the space.
حسنًا، فهو أشبه بشريحة خلال الفراغ.
We're here.
نحن هنا.
This is the equation of the hyper plane, and this is the equation of this plane.
هاهي المعادلة الخاصة بالمستوى الفائق، وها هي المعادلة الخاصة بهذا المستوى.
So we have w0, which is our intercept, just where this plane lives up and
فنجد أن لدينا w0 وهو الحاصر حيث يتحرك المستوى إلى أعلى و
down on the y-axis.
أسفل على محور y.
And we have w1 times the number of square feet, and
ولدينا w1 مضروبة في قيمة المساحة بالقدم المربع، و
w2 times the number of bathrooms.
w2 مضروبة في عدد الحمامات.
But a question is where do we stop?
ولكن السؤال هو أين نتوقف؟
Do we just want to include the number of bathrooms as our additional feature?
هل علينا أن نضم عدد الحمامات فقط كخاصية إضافية؟
There are lots of things we could think about including.
هناك الكثير من الأمور الأخرى التي يمكننا أن نفكر في ضمها.
We could think about in addition to our square feet, number of bathrooms,
يمكننا أن نفكر في المساحة بالقدم المربع، عدد الحمامات،
there's the number of bedrooms, the lot size, how old the house is, and
وهناك عدد غرف النوم، حجم الحصة في الأرض، عمر المنزل و
the list goes on and on.
وتستمر القائمة.
In terms of different properties of the house that could be influential in
وبها الكثير من الخواص الأخرى المختلفة للمنزل والتي يمكن أن تؤثر في
assessing it's value.
تقييم سعر المنزل.
But we're gonna actually hold off on this question of looking at which features
ولكننا سوف ننتظر على هذا السؤال حول البحث عن الخصائص
are important for this regression task, until we get to the regression course.
المهمة لخطوة الانحسار حتى نصل إلى مساق الانحسار.
So go to the regression course to learn more about this topic.
ولذلك يمكنك الذهاب إلى مساق الانسحار لتتعلم أكثر عن هذا الموضوع.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]